kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
I won't count on you.
I will go by myself.
Wait. I'll go, too.
I promised Hinata that I would
definitely protect you, princess.
With Hinata...?
She fought with the second Janin
and got hurt badly.
Hinata did...?
You guys said that you didn't accept
the mission of protecting me.
Then why do you concern
yourselves with me?
I...
Not only me,
but Hinata and Choji, too.
We don't like it when somebody
before us is hurt or sad. That's all.
Well, let's go!
If we pass through the valley ahead of us,
we'll get to the town.
If we do that, they probably won't
chase us all the way there!
Death Sentence
Cloudy with a Chance of Sun
Too bad, but you guys won't be able
to reach that village.
Since you guys are going to die here!
Why is he floating in the air?
Hey, kid, I bet a low-class Ninja like you
can't even imagine my Jutsu.
Take this!
Naruto!
I'm okay.
But what just flew at me?
Don't waste your time fighting me.
I have already captured
all three of your friends.
What?
Just hand over the girl.
If you do that, I'll spare your friends.
Choji and Hinata...
So, what are you going to do, kid?
Naruto, are you going
to abandon me, too?
Oh, no, this princess is telling you
to save her
and let your friends die.
Well, I don't mind that kind of thinking
since it's the same as mine.
Same as yours?
That's right.
If someone is useful,
then you should make use of them,
even though they may be
your siblings.
There is one thing I need
to thank you guys for.
Thank us? For what?!
For doing in Ruiga and Jiga.
I was going to put an end to them myself
sooner or later, anyway.
What...?
It was clear
that they would soon tell me:
"Big Brother, give us the property
and the money, too."
Three feudal lords are not necessary
in one country.
And you still call yourselves brothers?!
It doesn't matter.
Whether it's my parents
or my brothers,
I'll make use of anything I can.
Now, give her to me.
I refuse.
I see.
Naruto...
A person who would abandon
his siblings
would never keep his promise with me.
Well, that's true.
It's impossible, Naruto!
You don't even know
what kind of Jutsu it is!
That doesn't matter!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Take this!
What is this guy?
There's something hard around
his body that I can't see.
Naruto!
I'm sorry, but none
of your Ninjutsu works on me.
Not even one.
Damn it!
What...?
What is that?
Crystallized ice...?
I can gather water vapor in the air
and instantly turn it
into crystallized ice.
So, the things that just attacked me
were ice Shuriken.
Man! It's hard to see
if it's transparent ice.
Just that is not too interesting.
What is this great sense of danger?
I'm sure his Jutsu has already started!
Where is it?
Where is it coming from?!
Kid, do you know
today's weather forecast?
Weather forecast?
Cloudy and partly sunny.
It's good weather for you to die in.
What is this?
What?!
Look out!
— Damn it!
— Naruto!
— That's a lens!
— Lens?!
Yup, I turned
the crystallized ice into lens
to gather the sunlight and shoot it.
So, I can't really control it,
but it'll be an instant when you die.
As soon as the battle condition
at the Land of Green is prepared,
I'll burn up the surrounding countries
with this Jutsu.
This way!
It's no use.
I can even see things
that are a thousand miles away.
I found you.
Naruto... Why do you protect me?
I wonder why.
I don't know either.
Naruto...
Haruna.
While I distract him, run!
Don't even think you guys can get away
from my Jutsu by doing that!
You decided to hand over the princess?
Who would hand over Haruna
to the likes of you?!
What a fool.
I'm telling you that if you hand over
the selfish princess
and go back to the village,
I'll let your friends go.
I promised Hinata
that I would save Haruna!
Just to keep a promise to your friend,
you're gonna risk your life to fight
in a hopeless battle, huh?
You're just like the feudal lord
in Land of Green.
A big, good-natured fool!
Same as my father...
You're just like the feudal lord
in Land of Green.
A big, good-natured fool!
Same as my father...
This is what the feudal lord
foolishly said
to us who were trying to take over
the Land of Green:
"Please do not torment the people
in this country."
I beg you!
I don't care what happens to me,
but please promise me one thing!
This is a small, weak country
surrounded by big countries.
Without the powers of the people,
the country cannot prosper!
In order for the country to prosper,
we must take care of individual people
and not sacrifice a single life!
I want you to consider the people a family
and not torment them.
I am the feudal lord!
It doesn't matter what I do
to the people, right?
That's why...
That's why this country has been
at peace until now!
Peace doesn't matter to me.
All I need to do is use the people
as stepping stones
and feather my nest!
And because of that kind
of good nature,
his daughter was taken as a hostage!
What do you mean?!
It seems like it was ten years ago.
A lot of people were sacrificed
under pressure of the big country.
Riots occurred in the country
and the country came close to corruption.
It was a bitter decision.
I had no choice
but to let my daughter,
who is more important than my life,
be taken as a hostage.
I know that Haruna will not forgive me.
A cold-hearted father who sacrificed
his own daughter
just for the peace of the country.
Why don't you ask
your daughter directly?!
In the afterlife!
My father was... killed!
What an outrageously
good-natured person, huh?
You're wrong,
he was a great feudal lord!
Naruto...
Listen!
There are two kinds of human beings
in this world.
Those who use others,
and those who get used!
In my case,
I will get to the top using anyone,
whether it's my parents or my friends.
You...! I'll never forgive you!
Shut up!
Damn...!
Die!
Naruto.
You can't move anymore?!
You're not the one...
It was because of Haruna's father
that this country was peaceful.
The person who is going
to succeed this country is...
The person is...
Haruna!
Stop!
Stupid! Why aren't you running away?!
Kill me! If you kill me,
your goal will be fulfilled, right?!
Naruto... Naruto has nothing
to do with this!
So, both the father
and daughter are naive, after all.
Why not complain to your father
in the afterlife
for making you sacrifice your life
for the country?
How scary.
You...!
It's time for you to die, kid.
I'm not a kid!
My name is Uzumaki Naruto.
I'm not going to hand over
the Land of Green
to a person like you!
Naruto!
Die!
What?!
No... way.
But, kid, it's too late,
even though you took me down.
The Land of Green
without a feudal lord will collapse,
due to the war between
the larger countries over its territory.
Too bad, but that's not gonna happen!
Shizune!
It's a pain,
but we came to get you guys!
Shikamaru!
But I didn't ask you guys
to come get us!
But you look pretty beaten up.
No, no, this is...
Naruto!
Choji! Hinata! Yurinojou!
Everyone was safe!
Yeah. We were rescued
by the people of Leaf Village.
Huh? Oh, yeah, why are you guys here?
We received notice of a coup d'etat
in the Land of Green,
and Tsunade-sama herself ordered me
to come.
Princess Haruna's father was very kind
to Tsunade-sama and me.
My father?
Please forgive us, when we arrived,
your father was already...
I see. I've caused
so much trouble for you.
Damn!
The position of the feudal lord
that I finally got ahold of...
But then the surrounding countries
are not going to stay quiet.
It's okay.
An announcement has been sent out
to the neighbouring countries
in the name of the next feudal lord.
Under your name, Princess Haruna.
Then we don't need to worry about
the country getting attacked anymore!
Haruna!
Haruna.
Do it.
You want to take revenge
into your own hands, right?
I'd do the same if I were you.
I am... not like you!
Haruna...
Kikunojou, please forgive me.
Princess Haruna.
Here, Kikunojou could look over
the Land of Green.
I'm sure that Kikunojou will watch
over everyone forever.
Well, Lady Haruna, we are leaving now.
Thank you,
Naruto, Choji and Hinata.
Shizune, I'd like to ask a special favor.
What is it, Princess Haruna?
My role is to take over my father's will
to protect the peace of Land of Green.
In order to do that,
I want to borrow some help
from the Leaf Village.
— Our help?
— Yes.
I want you to lend me Naruto.
Please, Naruto.
Princess Haruna.
I want you to help me
with the revival of the Land of Green.
I... I...
I'm sorry,
but I can't really do that.
I need to go back to my friends.
And I need to do more training
and become much stronger.
There are things that I must do.
It's all for my precious friends!
Then I can't take you away from them.
Naruto, I'll promise that I will do
my best to keep my father's wishes
and strive for a peaceful country
where no one will be sacrificed.
Yeah! It's a promise!
Thank you! Naruto!
Goodbye, everybody!
We'll come back someday!
— Bye!
— See ya!
kinou wa Call Sign zenbu keitai de
yesterday's call sign was broadcast all from my phone
norenai Fuzz Guitar henna kouen de
in a strange park I play the fuzz guitar without enthusiasm
norenai fuzz guitar henna kouen de
Yellow Moon
yellow moon
ima mo mittsu kazoete me wo akete
even now, counting to three I open my eyes
Shadow Moon mada yume wo miteru
shadow moon, I am still dreaming
me wo mite me wo mite se wo mukeai nagara
look at my eyes, look at my eyes, as we face one another's back
me wo mite itsu aeru
look at my eyes, when can we meet?
Every Day Every Night omoi tsuku kotoba de
every day, every night, with every word I can think of
chirakatta mama no kimochi wo ima sugu
right away, my messy feelings as is
mahou no Chord Change nemurenai machi
a magical chord change in a restless city
higawari na Jazz Guitar sotto mainaa de
a daily jazz guitar played in a soft minor key
No! He's looking over here!
Of course, he'll look!
Stop complaining and attack him!
No, no, it's impossible!
He just moved right now!
He moved, Naruto!
Of course, he'll move!
Hey, approach him more!
No, no, no. This is my limit.
Come on, just give him
a one good hit!
No, the enemy is that thing you know?
A monster, a monster!
This wouldn't be a mission!
Next time:
"Ino Screams! Plump ♥ Paradise."